Responsive design, I know. [LAUGH] It's fun to resize your web browser and
see which sites resize gratefully and which sites remain defiantly large with
gross horizontal scroll bars. But responsive design is not just for
the web. Today, the lines between phones and tablets are disappearing. So
it's important to think about your UI will scale in our multiscreen world.
Don't be overwhelmed. Just like designing responsive layouts for the web,
build your layouts to be reasonably flexible or within a common device size.
Then you can set break points, providing alternative layouts for
those various sizes. Think about it this way,
small phone, large phone, medium tablet, and large tablet.